- ConversationTopicId: 06_MSQ_01_TalkFrancis
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_01_TalkFrancis_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_01_TalkFrancis_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0612_TalkBard
  PlayerPrompt: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: 0612_TalkBard_passion,0612_TalkBard_intellect,0612_TalkBard_joker
- ConversationTopicId: 0612_TalkBard_passion
  PlayerPrompt: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_passionPrompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_passionResponse"
  AchievementUnlock: narrativeprofile_passion_stillwater
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0612_TalkBard_intellect
  PlayerPrompt: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_intellectPrompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_intellectResponse"
  AchievementUnlock: narrativeprofile_intellect_stillwater
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0612_TalkBard_joker
  PlayerPrompt: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_jokerPrompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0612_MSQ_03_TalkBard_jokerResponse"
  AchievementUnlock: narrativeprofile_joker_stillwater
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_FrancisTurner_Lost
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_FrancisTurner_Lost_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_FrancisTurner_Lost_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_SaatvikAgrawal_Windmills
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_Windmills_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_Windmills_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LijsbetDeVries_Trapped
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_06_FarmerLijsbet_Bark_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_06_FarmerLijsbet_Bark"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_MichaelLewis_Trapped
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_06_FarmerMichael_Bark_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_06_FarmerMichael_Bark"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_Trapped
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_06_DruidNessa_Bark_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_06_DruidNessa_Bark_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_MichaelLewis_Farm
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_MichaelLewis_Farm_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_MichaelLewis_Farm_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LijsbetDeVries_Farm
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_LijsbetDeVries_Farm_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_LijsbetDeVries_Farm_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_TalkNessa
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_Nessa_talkto_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_06_RescueFarmers_Nessa_talkto_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_Druids
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_NessaHarrower_Druids_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_NessaHarrower_Druids_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LeovixSilva_Fallen
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_LeovixSilva_Fallen_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_LeovixSilva_Fallen_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_GideonStormsbane_Rescue
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_GideonStormsbane_Rescue_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06_GideonStormsbane_Rescue_response_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_FrancisTurner_Tribute
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_FrancisTurner_Tribute_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_FrancisTurner_Tribute_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_MarcelDupont_Tribute
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_MarcelDupont_Tribute_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_MarcelDupont_Tribute_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_GraceOMalley_Pirates
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_GraceOMalley_Pirates_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_GraceOMalley_Pirates_response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_TalkGrace
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_TalkGrace_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_TalkGrace"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_Success
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_Nessa_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_13_ReturnMiradorJewel_Nessaresponse_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LeovixSilva_Betrayal
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_LeovixSilva_Betrayal_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06_LeovixSilva_Betrayal_response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_MarcelDupont_Jewel
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_MarcelDupont_Jewel_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06_MarcelDupont_Jewel_response_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_FrancisTurner_Jewel
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_FrancisTurner_Jewel_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06_FrancisTurner_Jewel_response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_Medea_Eldergate
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_Medea_Eldergate_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_Medea_Eldergate_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_SaatvikAgrawal_NewSpeaker
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_NewSpeaker_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_NewSpeaker_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_Korrapati
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_NessaHarrower_Korrapati_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_NessaHarrower_Korrapati_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LeovixSilva_Closure
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_LeovixSilva_Closure_prompt_new"
  NPCResponse: "@06_LeovixSilva_Closure_response_a_new"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_OtherJewel
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal_next_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal_next_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_GraceOMalley_ToTown
  PlayerPrompt: "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal_next2_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06A_MSQ_14_SolveMapPuzzle_proposal_next2_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_GraceOMalley_Revolution
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_GraceOMalley_Revolution_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_GraceOMalley_Revolution_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_SaatvikAgrawal_Pirates
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_Pirates_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_SaatvikAgrawal_Pirates_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_NessaHarrower_Jewel
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_NessaHarrower_Jewel_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_NessaHarrower_Jewel_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_LeovixSilva_Caravan
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_LeovixSilva_Caravan_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_LeovixSilva_Caravan_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_Medea_Tribute
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_Medea_Tribute_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_Medea_Tribute_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_AhuraFarid_SpreadJoy
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_AhuraFarid_SpreadJoy_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_AhuraFarid_SpreadJoy_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_PriyaThakur_SpreadJoy
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_PriyaThakur_SpreadJoy_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_PriyaThakur_SpreadJoy_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_UtkarshSingh_SpreadJoy
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_UtkarshSingh_SpreadJoy_prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_UtkarshSingh_SpreadJoy_response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0623_Fisher_ExplainHotspots
  PlayerPrompt: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 0923_Fisher_ExplainHotspots
  PlayerPrompt: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@0223_Fisher_ExplainHotspots_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_Gunter_FirstLight
  PlayerPrompt: "@06_Gunter_FirstLight_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_Gunter_FirstLight_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 02_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 04_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@04_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 05_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@05_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 06_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@06_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 07_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@07_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 08_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@08_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 11_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@11_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 12_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@12_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 13_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@13_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 15_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@15_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 16_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@16_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 10_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@10_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 03_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@03_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
- ConversationTopicId: 14_00_Outfitter_Transmog
  PlayerPrompt: "@02_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Prompt"
  NPCResponse: "@14_00_Outfitter_Transmog_Response_a"
  AchievementUnlock: ""
  RequiredAchievement: ""
  RequiredFaction: ""
  RequiredLevel: ""
  ProvidedTopics: ""
